

MITCHELL HARDEN GRAPHIC DESIGNER

## CONTACTS



Aeromitch@gmail.com



316 - 249 - 3323



behance.net/mitchellharden

## REFERENCES

Lynette White Office Manager Wholesale Fireworks 316 - 200 - 8350 Lynette@wholesalefireworks.biz

Jordan Chamberlain Dispatcher Watco Transportation Services 866 - 386 - 9321 jchamberlain@watco.com

Kami Kanz **Graphic Designer** Curo Financial Technologies 612 - 360 - 4950

Paul **Production Manager** Print Me A Sian 316 - 655 - 0592 Paul@printmeasign.com

## HOBBIES

















## ABOUT ME

I'm a freelance interactive designer based in Wichita, Kansas, with a rich background in graphic design spanning over ten years. My true passion lies in torytelling through dynamic and engaging user experiences, particularly in the realms of websites and mobile apps.

In my career, I've traversed traditional graphic design and print, but my heart beats fastest when making things move and creating excitement through nnovative design. What sets me apart is my commitment to transforming the digital landscape. I aim to inject more interactivity into online platforms, crafting experiences that not only captivate but entice users to revisit.

### **EDUCATION**

2005 - 2008 Wichita State University Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design

2001 - 2003 **Butler Community College** Associate of Arts in Graphic Design

1998 - 2001 Derby High School

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2020- Current

**US Logo** 

#### **Graphic Designer**

My Position at US Logo is their screen print designer. I am in charge of designing logos for clients. Mocking up what the screen print is going to look like and e-mailing that to the clients. I am in charge of quality control for the overall prints. I also help with designing flyers, Business cards, any signage design, Embroidery, and vehicle wraps. I use Adobe programs for all of my design needs.

2014 - 2020

#### Print me a sign / Wholesale Fireworks Art Director / Graphic Designer / Print Shop Manager

I am in charge of all the design work and advertisements for our clients. I take great pride in the designs I create for our customers. I talk to the client to find out what their company is about and send them proofs of their designs. Once they have chosen a final design I set up our HP printers and start producing their jobs. I am also in charge of all production, shipping, billing and closing out each job.

2009 - 2013

#### **Select Homes Graphic Designer**

While at Select Homes I designed their real estate magazine that came out every month. I was the only designer they had to get their magazine on the shelf before the month it was advertising for. I also designed the business cards for all of the different employees and any other in house letters.

## Design Services





look and feel thru out the application.

# INTERACTION DESIGN Ruild an intactive website or app that is pleaseing to look at and enjoyable to use

needs for marketing.

GRAPHIC DESIGN





